[Disclaimer: This series is entirely fictional
and solely for entertainment purposes
with no association or reference
to any individuals, places, or events;
there may be inappropriate behaviors
and vulgarity based on the character's persona;
viewer discretion is advised]
I thought you were not going to come.
What do you want?
I just want to help you...
maintain that fake happiness
for a long time.
Tell me what you want.
Five hundred thousand baht.
Five hundred thousand?!
I have no idea what you are asking me,
but if it's time to say it,
I'm going to tell you the truth.
The entrance
is decorated with stones to make customers
feel confident in our restaurant as they enter.
The floor in the middle
is made of swirl-patterned wood,
resembling the continuous flow
of water energy
to attract many customers.
You pay attention to
every detail, don't you?
Exactly.
Also, each private room
is differently decorated.
Different, but still matching.
But every room is already booked today.
I'll give you the photos of them instead
so that you can use them for your study.
Thank you so much.
This is what we call
a masterful blend
of superstition
and design theory.
A perfect balance.
Let's have lunch together before you go.
I want you to try our food here.
I guarantee that the food
is as stunning as the decoration.
Oh, unfortunately,
I have a meeting
at the university after this.
Maybe next time.
Let's split up, okay?
- Goodbye.
Excuse me, I'd like to use the toilet.
It's over there.
Go straight and turn left.
Thank you.
♫Is it pure coincidence?♫
♫Or is it destiny that decides?♫
♫Is someone above drawing all these lines?♫
♫Or playing matchmaker in disguise?♫
♫What if the stars shift in their place♫
♫Slightly out of line,♫
♫Will our orbits still align?♫
♫Try answering if your world
will cross with mine♫
♫Though the destiny between us
is differently defined♫
♫And I believe our love has power♫
♫I believe the love of us♫
♫Will realign the stars back to the line
where they should be♫
Let's go Dutch.
You can transfer your share to my account.
You're still a treasurer
of our classroom as always.
Yeah, has our classroom's leader
changed the status from being single yet?
I'm protective
of my single life, you know?
Whoa.
- Protective of your single life, huh?
- But Pitcha, a future famous artist,
isn't allowed to be
someone's sweetheart, right?
A secret of people in the industry
can't be exposed, you know?
So dramatic, huh?
Wait.
What if we dig up the old photos
of your sweetheart?
Am I going to get a backlash?
Why on earth would you do that?
For social media engagement, you know?
It's the point of having
a celebrity friend.
Enough. Stop it.
- Let's settle the bill.
- Let's transfer it.
- I totally forgot.
- I almost forgot that.
Let's go.
Hey, guys.
Who wants a ride back with me?
Me. I'll go with you.
You can drop me off at the train station.
What about you, Pitcha?
I'll take him home.
Whoa.
Doing a task for the old sweetheart
as always, huh?
Be careful. If his fans see this,
this can become news.
But if I wear these sunglasses,
they'll have no idea who I am.
- What are you doing?
- That's okay.
You don't need to do this.
Shall we have some selfies
together before we go?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Come on.
Pure,
look at what I just sent you.
Before we end, don't forget
to ask the tarot and me
for forgiveness.
The last prophecies were so accurate
that they brought you here again, right?
You just had a reading
not so long ago, though.
Yeah, that's right.
Now,
many things
are starting to come true.
By the way, has Ritt,
the Prophecy Stone Master, quit reading?
He has quit for a while.
I'm his replacement.
I can assure you that
I am just as accurate.
Thank you so much.
What are you doing here?
I just...
want to warn you
that you're running out of time.
Don't let me wait long.
Otherwise...
you probably know what will happen next.
Ployplern,
where is Pure?
Maybe at the back.
Hey, Ritt!
Can you test a new deck for me?
Just pick a card. That's all.
Please, please.
Let's test my accuracy,
Ployplern, the Pictura Master.
If it comes out like this, it means...
Check on all customers, okay?
Don't let them wait.
Hey...
You forgot the stones at my bar again.
You saw the photo I sent you, right?
They finally met each other.
I don't know when they met.
What should I do, huh?
But they looked completely fine.
About this...
I...
You two should settle it yourselves.
Pure
sent me that photo.
Today,
you were also in that restaurant, right?
Well...
Pitcha and I...
Did you know from the beginning
that I wasn't your childhood sweetheart?
You know I've lied to you.
- Well...
- Was it really fun?
And Pitcha
also knew
that I've been impersonating him, right?
How could you guys do this?
Do you think I'm some kind of clown?
Have you been waiting
to see how long I could lie to you?
It's not like that.
I thought
I was so talented
that I could make you believe me
without any doubt.
But...
the more talented one is actually you.
You made me believe with all my heart
that what happened between us was real,
even though it was all our lies.
Please let me explain first.
What else do you want me to hear?!
The next lie you're going to tell?!
Be honest!
What else should I know
about your make-up stories?
Liars like us,
who love to make up stories,
aren't supposed to be together.
It's not going to work anyway.
I'm sorry.
Can you let me explain?
I love you so much,
but how could you do this to me?
How?
I'm so sorry.
Let's go home and talk it out.
Let's talk it out when we're home, okay?
Please.
Hey, Ritt.
You came home pretty late, huh?
Have you had anything yet?
Excuse me, I'll go pack my things.
Why pack?
When we were young, it was the same.
One day, we wanted to be so close
that we couldn't even breathe.
But the other, we didn't even
want to see each other's faces.
What finally happened, you know?
We still ended up eating
at the same dining table anyway.
Don't let the problem
last overnight.
Letting it last overnight
can turn a small issue
into something bigger.
Yes, Grandpa.
Even though it starts with a fight,
it must end with reconciliation.
With your lover,
it's better to compromise.
Therefore, go settle it properly,
and get back together.
Yes, Grandpa.
Do Grandpa and Grandma
know everything, too?
Grandma does,
but Grandpa doesn't.
What about the three feng shui masters,
their prophecies,
and the wedding?
Those were also your plans, right?
Grandma and I planned them
because we wanted you to stay with us.
Thanks a lot.
Overall...
In the past,
there wasn't anything real at all, right?
You probably just wanted
to make love with me
and treated me as someone
to satisfy your sexual desire, didn't you?
It wasn't like that.
I've started these lies,
so getting out of your life
and everyone else's here
might be the best apology I could give.
I'm not going to judge
who is right or wrong.
But I just want to let you know this.
"With lies,
your relationship can never go further."
The foundation of love is sincerity,
not lies.
Lies might help us avoid the problems
today, tomorrow,
or even the day after tomorrow,
but they can't help us every day.
Right, Grandma?
"Telling a lot of lies to others
will make you lie to yourself at the end."
Is there anything you want to tell me?
You, too.
Itthi.
Are you two keeping something from me?
We're family, you know?
Isn't it better to tell the truth
to each other?
I'm this old.
I don't want your secrets
to be harder than my sickness.
What did you know?
Did anyone tell you something?
No one had to tell me anything.
I saw it with my own eyes.
I saw your worried eyes
every time you looked at me,
as if I'm about to disappear soon or something.
The changes among people
living in the same house
can be sensed through their eyes.
Did you think I couldn't figure it out?
You, too, Itthi.
At this age, haven't you known me yet?
Life is like brewing tea.
Whether it's sweet or bitter,
it depends on the drinkers' minds
by the time they drink it.
I'm not afraid of death at all,
but I'm afraid
I won't get to spend enough time
laughing with you two
before passing away.
So, from now on,
don't lie to me anymore.
Don't say it's good if it's actually not.
If you want to cry, just cry.
Tell me whatever you want to tell.
Life is shorter than you think.
Don't waste your time
on acting to each other.
Be honest with one another.
Don't lie to people
in the same house, okay?
I'm sorry.
I don't want you to worry.
Seeing you sick
makes us feel sick, too.
So I just thought that
keeping this from you
could make you happy for a few more days.
We wanted your remaining days
to be as happy as possible.
I'm not going to die soon.
Cancer just comes to warn me.
To make me realize
that I should take care of my health more.
You, too, Itthi.
Don't bring those three fake
feng shui masters here again.
They weren't good at acting at all.
You know that?
Of course, I do!
Belief and faith
are sometimes like a walking stick
that supports our spirit,
so I used those three feng shui masters
as our moral support.
Good prophecies
are sometimes healthy
for our minds, aren't they?
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much, Itthi.
But from now on,
you have to tell me only the truth, okay?
No more lies.
Yeah.
Also, Itthi,
go settle it properly with Ritt.
No matter what, bring him back.
There is only one trick
I'm going to share with you.
Persistence is key.
Right?
I've always been using this trick.
Your grandma
surrendered to me
because of my persistence, you know?
Got it, Grandpa.
Come on, let me have a hug.
You should get into a wheelchair first.
It's okay.
Alright, walk carefully.
Your mother looks much stronger.
She doesn't need a walking stick anymore.
She has recently started doing
physical therapy on her own.
Come on, Mom.
Hey, do you see?
I can walk much better on my own now.
Very good of you, Mom.
Soon, you'll be able to sit in the front row,
cheering on a newbie idol in Korea soon.
Huh?
Did I just miss something?
Are you going to get back to auditioning?
Since when? Why didn't you tell me that?
Well...
I'm not sure yet.
I just think that
there are a lot of things I want to do now
before flying back.
The opportunity you've got
is what many people want to have.
Don't let it go.
I know.
But sometimes, where we really want to be
matters more than the opportunities we have.
So, where do you really want to be?
If I guess, that probably is...
making other people happy,
like when he taught
the younger ones dance.
Sometimes,
I just want to be somewhere
that can bring peace to my mind.
I understand
that your whole life might have felt restricted,
whether because of me,
or the agency there.
But I also want to see you
live with happiness.
And happiness
will come to you
when you are brave enough to choose
and brave enough to lose.
No matter which way you choose,
I'll always be here
to see your success.
Me, too.
Thank you, Mom.
So, this can be the order
for the presentation.
Does anyone have any questions
about the final presentation?
Is there a second chance
in case we don't pass?
Don't get used to
getting a second or third chance.
For some things,
if you miss your chance, that's it.
So,
don't expect a second chance.
Some opportunities
only present themselves once.
Got it, professor.
Well,
if you don't have any questions,
see you on the presentation day.
I'm rooting for you all.
Is there anything
that I should know?
What else haven't you told me yet?
- Be careful, Mom.
- Okay.
Thank you so much.
I think I'm going to go to my room.
I just want to take some rest.
And you, check the fridge to see
if there's anything to eat.
Warm it up for Pure, too, okay?
Yes, Mom.
You can sit down
and catch your breath first, Pure.
You gave me a ride all morning.
Yes, Mom.
Take care of your friend.
Thank you so much for taking us home.
No problem.
I feel like your mom is my mom,
the same way that you and I
are like the same person.
By saying this,
do you want to go back to Korea with me?
Let me be one of your fans
who waits for you here.
When you have a concert in Thailand,
I'll immediately book a front-row ticket.
Okay.
Are you hungry?
What do you want to have?
What can I have?
So, what do you want?
Mmm... Can I have this one?
Hey, what are you doing?
What if Mom sees it?
I just want to have you.
I'm hungry.
Let me enjoy you now
before you become famous without me there.
Whoa.
Is this the only thing on your mind, huh?
It isn't like that. Don't get me wrong.
You just said it.
I can't deny
that I've been obsessed
with you since that night.
There you go.
But...
Listen to me first.
That isn't all.
The more I look at you...
the more I want to know you.
The closer I get to you,
the deeper I want to go.
How deep?
Deep enough to reach your dream
you've never told anyone about.
Deep enough to your fear
that has been kept inside you.
Deep enough to reach your true self,
the one you're afraid to show anyone,
even your mother.
I want to know Pitcha,
who doesn't have to be great,
be forced,
or do anything for others.
The one...
who can't hide anything from me.
I also mean that thing.
You're mischievous.
I really want to get to know you better.
Really?
It's true.
If so...
I'll let you know me
deeper than you ever have before.
Are you okay?
Okay with what?
With...
So you're going to leave
after you're finished?
Of course.
What do you want me to do
after finishing, huh?
I'm kidding.
Making a sulky face, huh?
Gotcha.
Do you have a sensitive side as well?
You're so mischievous,
always teasing me.
It's because you're so easy to tease.
My feelings for you aren't
just when we're in bed.
If that were the case,
I might not feel this way...
every time I see your face.
What do you mean by
"this way"?
I mean
I'm afraid that one day, you'll be so famous
that you won't remember me.
But I'm willing to let you forget me
if that's the way you've chosen.
Don't you want to hold me back,
so I can stay with the girls,
or even with you?
I know you have your own path
to reach your dream.
I'm not going to hold you back.
I don't even want to do that,
but there is one thing I want you to know.
I genuinely have
a good feeling about you.
As genuinely as anyone could possibly feel.
Thank you for that.
I also hope that
no matter how far apart we are,
there will still be a day
when you miss me.
Just a little bit is fine.
Whether I live in Korea
or anywhere else,
I'll never forget that, once,
we were
in each other's arms like this.
I'm truly glad we got to know each other.
Are you leaving?
I think I'm going to check
how Ritt is doing for a bit.
Mmm.
I'm not sure who
I should feel more sorry for.
They did it to themselves.
Fooling each other as if they were kids.
You can feel sorry for me first.
Sorry for what?
For my short time of happiness with you.
In just a little while...
you'll leave me far behind.
What?
What kind of person are you
to make others feel guilty with your words?
Before you go,
can we do it every day?
Jeez!
I really mean it.
Please.
- Please, please.
- No, stop it.
- Hey...
Let's do it again.
Hey, that's enough.
One more time, please.
Hey, you!
That's enough. You're going to wake my mom up.
You, stop. Stop it.
Okay, fine.
Here. In case you get hungry.
Thanks.
How are you, though?
What am I supposed to say?
Actually,
I've always been trying
to make you tell Itthi the truth,
- but you still...
- I know!
I know it was my fault.
Are you here just to pile on me?
And for Pitcha,
he also didn't want to
help Itthi trick you,
- but he just...
- You...
knew that Pitcha knew about this?
You knew all of this
was part of the plan of...
When did you know it?
Your friend, Master Ritt,
should take some acting classes,
or screenwriting courses.
Why did you say that?
Because he's impersonating me
and lying to Itthi that
he's his sweetheart.
Who told you this?
Well...
You have to help me out.
I really like this person.
But tricking him like this...
How is this going to work out?
He tricked me first,
so I just tricked him back. It's fair.
Fine,
I'll help you.
But where is it again?
I'll send you the bar's location.
What's the name of the bar?
Magic Move.
It's a new bar near my campus.
Okay.
Please handle it for me.
You really like him, huh?
Actually,
Itthi asked me to see Master Ritt for a reading.
You've known about it for so long,
but you didn't tell me.
You let me become a clown
in everyone's eyes.
I just wanted to know
what you would do next.
- Also, Pitcha...
- Stop it.
Do you know...
that you're my best friend, Pure?
And I love you so much.
But look what you did to me.
It isn't what you think at all.
- I just...
- I'm really hurt...
that he tricked me.
But my best friend
was even in on it as well.
Who can I still trust in this world?
Hey, Ritt.
Thanks for coming.
I'm so impressed.
I used to think
that at least
I had a friend
who'd always be by my side.
But now I realize
that I...
don't have anyone sincere left anymore.
I can't feel any worse than this.
Just get out of my room.
[Ansuz: communication and revelation]
Guess it's time for the truth
to speak for itself instead of prophecies.
Look over there.
Thank you so much.
Hey!
What?!
- What?!
- They're just snacks.
Enough with the "Hey, hey, hey."
I'm shipping this.
- Are you two a thing?
- I just bought him some snacks.
So sweet of you!
- Here is your drink.
- Thanks.
No matter how hard I try,
nothing will ever change.
But now...
it hurts a lot more.
Their prophecies
and the wedding?
Those were also your plans, right?
Liars like us,
who love to make up stories,
aren't supposed to be together.
It's not going to work anyway.
Can you please come back?
Ritt.
I still want to explain.
I didn't mean for it to turn out that way.
It started when you...
Whether you meant it or not,
it doesn't matter anymore.
That's enough, Itthi.
Let it end this way.
I still believe that
the sincerity between us
can fix this.
- Let's begin...
- Listen.
I've indeed used those stones
to deceive you
and others.
But do you know
what's more deceptive than my prophecies?
It's your words that sounded heartfelt.
I don't think we can fix it anymore.
The only thing we can do
is not let those lies
and fake feelings escalate any further.
Let's accept that,
up until now,
our love was never real to begin with.
I'll take it.
And let's end it here.
Fooling each other...
In the end,
you can't avoid the truth anyway.
If he did what you did,
it's fair game, isn't it?
If you rob a thief,
you become a thief.
Fate brought two people together.
Coincidences don't usually happen.
If you want to keep him safe,
give me one million baht.
Where is Ritt?
♫Is it pure coincidence?♫
♫Or is it destiny that decides?♫
♫Is someone above drawing all these lines?♫
♫Or playing matchmaker in disguise?♫
♫What if the stars shift in their place♫
♫Slightly out of line,♫
♫Will our orbits still align?♫
♫Try answering if your world
will cross with mine♫
♫Though the destiny between us
is differently defined♫
♫I believe our love will change our♫
♫Destiny, rewrite prophecies♫
♫Even if they are against our destiny♫
♫(But we're gonna try, try, try)♫
♫And I believe our love has power♫
♫I believe the love of us♫
♫Will realign the stars back to the line
where they should be♫
♫(And we're gonna try, try, try)♫